#### Contact

4022396584 (Mobile) sheldonhollis1993@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/sheldon-hollis-576a93278 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Blogging

E-Books

Case Studies

# Sheldon Hollis

Freelance Ghostwriter and Copywriter/Content Writer Omaha, Nebraska, United States

## Summary

Hello, my name is Sheldon Hollis and I am a professional Ghostwriter and Copywriter. Writing has been a passion of mine since I was a child. I look forward, every day, to the journey of becoming an even better writer. When given the opportunity, I pour my heart and soul into whatever project I am assigned. I write to ensure that I make your dreams a reality.

I offer the following writing services:

Fictional Ghostwriting
Copywriting
Content Writing

Please, send me a message if you're interested. I promise you will be satisfied and looking forward to our next writing journey.

## Experience

Hollis Daily Writing
11 years 11 months

Copywriter

January 2012 - Present (11 years 11 months)

Remote

My experience as a copywriter has allowed me to work with some of the most ambitious entrepreneurs across a variety of fields. I specialize, primarily, in direct sales copy where I specialize in writing the text of persuasive sales pitches intended to convince potential buyers to make a purchase. Whether it's a landing page to entice prospective customers to act quickly before they miss out on a good deal or a blog to inform current customers about new products or services, I will always find the right words to close the deal.

A list of the following:

- Landing Pages & Sales Pages

- Headers
- Launch Emails
- Product Descriptions
- Social Media Ads
- Social Media Posts
- Slogans and Taglines

#### **Content Writer**

January 2012 - Present (11 years 11 months)

Remote

A list of the following:

- Blogs and Articles
- Case Studies
- Email Newsletters
- Commercial/Ad Scripts
- E-Books

#### Hollis Daily Witting

Ghostwriter

January 2012 - Present (11 years 11 months)

Remote

I am a professional ghostwriter who specializes in writing fiction across multiple genres (mystery, romance, crime, sci-fi, and drama). I have personally published books on Amazon and Barnes and Noble. I have worked on projects with filmmakers and novelists who dared to achieve their dreams.

I specialize in the following areas:

- Screen Writing
- Short Story Writing
- Comic Book Writing
- Video Game Writing

Before you order, I suggest you check out my portfolio which is listed below. I promise, my words will give birth to your dreams.

### Education

Omaha Northwest Magnet High School
High School Diploma, High School/Secondary Diplomas and
Certificates · (August 2007 - May 2011)